[
    {
        "_id":"61mjiAkmfdisalksdmfsfas",
        "question":"what the deku real name ?",
        "options":[
            "isumaku midoria",
            "katsuku bakuga",
            "shotu toriyama",
            "hintat"
        ],
        "answer":"Isumaku midoria"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was the winner of U.A. Sports Festival Arc?",
        "options":[
            "Fumikage Tokoyami",
            "Shoto Todoroki",
            "Katsuki Bakugo",
            "Kai Chisaki"
        ],
        "answer":"Katsuki Bakugo"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is Katsuki Bakugo’s alias?",
        "options":[
            "Kacchan",
            "Sirius",
            "Power Loader",
            "Gran Torino"
        ],
        "answer":"Kacchan"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which one is not a member of the Hideout Raid Team?",
        "options":[
            "Edgeshot",
            "Tiger",
            "Mirko",
            "All Might"
        ],
        "answer":"Mirko"
    },
    {
        "question":"Anime season 1 consists of how many episodes?",
        "options":[
           "20",
           "14",
           "17",
           "13"
        ],
        "answer":"13"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who faced off Snipe in the final exam?",
        "options":[
            "Shoto Todoroki & Momo Yaoyorozu",
            "Mezo Shoji & Toru Hagakure",
            "Fumikage Tokoyami & Tsuyu Asui",
            "Kyoka Jiro & Koji Koda"
        ],
        "answer":"Mezo Shoji & Toru Hagakure"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is a “quirk”?",
        "options":[
            "a hero",
            "a superpower",
            "a batter",
            "an event"
        ],
        "answer":"a superpower"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is a “quirk”?",
        "options":[
            "a hero",
            "a superpower",
            "a batter",
            "an event"
        ],
        "answer":"a superpower"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was using the “magnetism” quirk?",
        "options":[
            "Kenji Hikiishi",
            "Shota Aizawa",
            "Tsunagu Hakamata",
            "Nemuri Kayama"
        ],
        "answer":"Kenji Hikiishi"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which one is not a “Pro Hero”?",
        "options":[
            "Blood Hero: Vlad King",
            "Death Arms",
            "Ectoplasm",
            "Overhaul"
        ],
        "answer":"Overhaul"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is All Might’s real name?",
        "options":[
            "Enji Todoroki",
            "Chizome Akaguro",
            "Toshinori Yagi",
            "Ochaco Uraraka"
        ],
        "answer":"Toshinori Yagi"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who is the principal of U.A. High School?",
        "options":[
            "Nezu",
            "Recovery Girl",
            "No. 13",
            "Lunch-Rush"
        ],
        "answer":"Nezu"
    }
]